Zhang Tianyou!
What on earth did you do to me?
Untie me right now!
You're asking what I did to you?
You should ask yourself what you did to me!
Look, just look!
Zhang Tianyou, what are you doing?
Forgive me.
Zhang Tianyou, untie me right now!
Last night, your fiery passion...
...was truly hard to control.
Your husband, on the other hand...
...has a weak constitution,
and couldn't withstand your wildness.
I had no choice but to resort to this.
You won't blame me, will you?
Young Master!
Qi Lianhai is dead.
His son is waiting downstairs.
My condolences, Young Master Qi.
Sitting before you is the Qi Family head.
Zhang Tianyou.
I really have to thank you.
There's no need to thank me.
This was all through your own effort.
Hand it over.
You mean...
The congratulatory gift?
The Sheng Family Curse Scripture and Mei Family Celestial Seal.
My father was killed by evil creatures.
Soon it'll be my turn.
Seven days to the Life-Returning Deadline.
Finding the Tidal Tomb can't be delayed.
The Chief candidate to find that tomb...
...must be outside The Four Great Families.
Didn't your father tell you?
I'll find this person myself.
But it absolutely can't be Zhang Tianyou.
Miss Mei.
Whatever the Mei Family is scheming,
do you think I don't know?
Look at this!
Look what you've done to her!
Stand back when you speak.
Hand it over.
Nobody move!
Mei Jiushuang,
I suggest you hurry back home.
Young Master Li is still waiting for you.
Qi Tiankun, what are you doing?
Cousin,
I've always remembered what you told me.
I've killed my brother now,
and I control the entire Qi Family.
I'll soon rid you of this useless live-in son-in-law.
Qi Tiankun,
you can't run wild in the Sheng Family.
Did you really think I fell for you?
Let me tell you,
you were just my tool to handle your brother!
And as for you two...
Miss Sheng, don't be impulsive.
I have the Celestial Seal and Earth Curse Scripture.
I'm the true head of the Sheng Family.
Zhang Tianyou,
I'll give you one last chance.
Her or me?
Excellent.
This is exactly the outcome I wanted to see.
I only want to find the Tidal Tomb now.
Men, drag her away!
Don't touch me, I can...
I said I can walk!
I... I can walk!
Let's go.
Lingyu.
You... You don't even like me.
Yet you made me do this...
What are you doing?
Get in.
Li Xiao.
Why are you here?
Jiushuang.
Don't touch me.
Jiushuang, are you okay?
Jiushuang, I know you've always been biased against me.
But I genuinely came here to find you.
I didn't expect them to lock me up.
You were already engaged to me,
yet you secretly hooked up with Wan Chun'er.
How can I possibly trust you?
Jiushuang, you've really misunderstood.
When I went to the Wan family before,
it was to discuss how, as Chief of The Four Great Families,
I'd find Dragon Seeker heirs for the Tidal Tomb.
I don't expect you to understand my good intentions.
Now the Qi and Sheng Family heads have died suddenly.
The Life-Returning Death Deadline is no rumor.
Jiushuang.
From now on, I will definitely protect you.
I'll play along with your little act for now,
to see what you're really plotting.
She actually fell for it.
Looks like I'm still as charming as ever.
Feiyan, what are you doing here?
We found where the Qi Family hid the original Talisman Book.
Here.
Zhang Tianyou,
About The Four Great Families' expedition 20 years ago,
what exactly is your connection to it?
Are you willing to give me a straight answer?
In seven days, when the moon is full,
if The Four Great Families can truly break the Death Limit,
I will naturally tell you.
If you don't want to tell me, forget it.
We're even now.
I never want to see you again.
Zhang Tianyou, who is she?
She's...
I'm his woman.
What?
What of it?
He'd rather fool around outside
than settle for a bratty canary like you.
No, no, no, that's not it!
We're not close.
We just...
slept together, that's all!
When did that happen?!
Zhang Tianyou!
Get out! All of you, get the hell out!
Get out of the Sheng Family!
This is it.
Young Master.
Are you sure the Qi Family hid the original Talisman Book here?
Leng Feiyan's Sand-Turning Gang
is quite skilled at locating tombs.
She wouldn't lie to me.
Qi Lianhai was just murdered.
She must have deduced this location from the clues.
Let's go in.
The Qi Family's Talisman Book should be inside.
Finding it gives us leverage against The Four Great Families.
What was that?
Let's go!